A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor Harry F. Byrd, 1926-1930
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Subject files, 1926-1930., Extent: 39.75 cu. ft. (106 boxes). (Box Boxes 1-105, 141)
  - Health, Catawba Sanitorium, 1927-1929. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Health, Commissioner, 1926-1930. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Health, State Board of, 1926-1928. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Health, State Board of, 1929-1930. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Henry, Patrick, Bust Commission, 1926. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Highway Commission, 1926 January - June. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Highway Commission, 1926 July - September. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Highway Commission, 1926 October - December. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Highway Commission, 1927 January - March. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Highway Commission, 1927 April - June. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Highway Commission, 1927 July - August. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Highway Commission, 1927 September. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Highway Commission, 1927 October - December. (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Highway Commission, 1928 January - February. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Highway Commission, 1928 March - April. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Highway Commission, 1928 May - June. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Highway Commission, 1928 July. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Highway Commission, 1928 August. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Highway Commission, 1928 September. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Highway Commission, 1928 October - December. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Highway Commission, 1929 January - February. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Highway Commission, 1929 March - April. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Highway Commission, 1929 May - June. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Highway Commission, 1929 July - August. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Highway Commission, 1929 September - October. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Highway Commission, Reports, 1929 September - October,. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Highway Commission, 1929 November - December. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Highway Commission, Positions with, 1926-1929. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Highway Commission, Vacancies, 1926-1927. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Highway Commission, Vacancies, H.B. Sproul, 1929. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Highway markers, 1929. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Highway meeting, Farmville (Va.), 1926-1927. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Highway meeting, Fredericksburg (Va.), 1927. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Highway meeting, Lexington (Va.), 1927. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Highway meeting, Marion (Va.), 1927. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Highway meeting, Purcellville (Va.), 1926-1927. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Highway meeting, South Hill (Va.), 1927. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Highway planting, 1929. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Highway routes, 1926-1927. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Honesty Campaign, 1929. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Hospitals, Central State, 1927-1928. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Hospitals, Commissioner of, 1926-1929. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Hospitals, Eastern State, 1926-1929. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Hospitals, Southwestern State, 1926-1929. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Hospitals, State Colony for Epileptic, Etc. (Colony, Va.), 1926-1929. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Hospitals, Western State, 1926-1928. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Hospitals, Western State, 1929-1930. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - I, 1926-1929. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Inauguration of President, 1929. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Indians, 1926-1929. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Institute of Public Affairs, 1927. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Industrial Commission, 1926-1927. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Industrial Commission, 1928. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Industrial Commission, 1929. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Industrial rehabilitation, 1926-1929. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Industries, New, 1926-1928. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Industries, New, 1928. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Industries, New, 1929. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Industries, New, 1929. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Industries, New, Covington Rayon, 1927-1928. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Inquiries, Miscellaneous, 1929-1930. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Institute of Public Affairs, 1927-1929. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Institute of Public Affairs, 1929. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Insurance Commission, 1926-1929. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Insurance Rate Commission, 1926-1929. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Interest rates, 1928. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - International Bank, 1927. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - International Advertising Convention, 1929. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - International Conference on Adult Education, 1929. (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - International Association of Public Employment Service, 1929. (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - International Suffrage Alliance, 1926. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1926-1928. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1926 January - February. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 1926 March. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Invitations, 1926 April. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Invitations, 1926 May. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Invitations, 1926 June. (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Invitations, 1926 July. (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Invitations, 1926 August. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1926 September. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1926 October. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1926 November. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1926 December. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1927 January. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1927 February. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1927 March. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 1927 April. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Invitations, 1927 May. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1927 June. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1927 July. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1927 August. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1927 September. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1927 October. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1927 November. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1927 December. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 1928 January. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1928 February. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1928 March. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1928 April. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1928 April. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1928 May. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1928 June. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1928 July. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Invitations, 1928 August. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1928 September. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1928 October. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1928 November. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1928 December. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1929 January. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1929 February. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1929 March. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1929 April. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1929 May. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1929 June. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, 1929 June. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, 1929 July. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Invitations, 1929 August. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Invitations, 1929 September. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 1929 October. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, 1929 November. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Invitations, 1929 December. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Invitations, Extended, 1926-1928. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Invitations, Extended, 1929-1930. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Izaak Walton League, 1929. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - J, 1926. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - J, 1927. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - J, 1928-1930. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Jamestown, 1928-1929. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Jefferson Centennial, 1926. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Jefferson Memorial, 1926. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Jefferson Memorial, 1927-1929. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Judges, 1926. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Judges, 1926. (Box 52, Folder 1-3)
  - Judges, 1926-1927. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Judges, 1927-1930. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Judges, Christian, Frank P., 1928. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Judges, Cox, Edwin P., 1928. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Judges, Crump, 1928. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Judges, Epes, Louis S., 1928. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Judges, Morrissette, C.H., 1926. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Judges, Peterson, M.R., 1928. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Judges, Roberts, Floyd H., 1928. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Judges, Smith, Howard W., 1928. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Judges, Recommendations to succeed Judge Tyler, 1927. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Judges, Recommendations to succeed Judge West, 1929. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Judges, Retired, 1928-1929. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Judges, Substitutes, 1927 April - May. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Judges, Substitutes, 1927 June - August. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Judges, Substitutes, 1927 July - December. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Judges, Substitutes, 1928 January - March. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Judges, Substitutes, 1928 April - May. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Judges, Substitutes, 1928 June - July. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Judges, Substitutes, 1928 August - December. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Judges, Substitutes, 1929 January - April. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Judges, Substitutes, 1929 May - August. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Judges, Substitutes, 1929 September - December. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Judges, Supreme Court, Judge Holt, 1928. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Judges, Supreme Court, New Constitution, 1928-1930. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Judges, Supreme Court, Miscellaneous, 1927-1929. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Judges, Danville (Va.), 1927. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Judges, Richmond (Va.), 1926. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Judges, Roanoke (Va.), 1926-1927. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Judges, 14th Judicial Circuit, 1927. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Judges, 16th Judicial Circuit, 1928. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Judges, 16th Judicial Circuit, Sinclair, C. Armistead, 1928. (Box 55, Folder 6-7)
  - Judges, 18th Judicial Circuit, 1928. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Judges, 26th Judicial Circuit, Moffett, W.F., 1929. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Judges, 26th Judicial Circuit, Alexander, J.R.H., 1929. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Judges, 26th Judicial Circuit, Miscellaneous, 1929. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Judicial Circuits, Redistricting, 1927. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Judicial Counsel, 1928-1929. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - K, 1926-1927. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - K, 1927-1929. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Kenmore Association, 1927-1929. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Kentucky, Governor, 1928-1929. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - L, 1926. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - L, 1927 January - April. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - L, 1927 April - June. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - L, 1927 July - 1928 September. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - L, 1928 October - 1930. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Labor Commissioner, 1926-1927. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Labor Commissioner, 1928-1929. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Labor Commissioner, 1929-1930. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Labor Commissioner, Recommendations, 1927. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Labor Commissioner, Recommendations, 1927-1928. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Labor and Industry, Bureau, 1925-1928. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Labor Officials Convention, 1927. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Land Grants, 1926-1929. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Law enforcement, 1926. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Law enforcement, 1927. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Law enforcement, 1928 January - June. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Law enforcement, 1928 July - December. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Law enforcement, 1929 January - April. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Law enforcement, 1929 May - August. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Law enforcement, 1929 September - 1930 January. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Law enforcement, Traffic violations, 1925-1928. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Lee Boulevard - Highway, 1926-1929. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Lee, Robert E., Memorial Foundation (Stratford, Va.), 1929. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Lee Statue, State Capitol (Richmond, Va.), 1927-1928. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Lee Statue, State Capitol (Richmond, Va.), 1929 January - April. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Lee Statue, State Capitol (Richmond, Va.), 1929 May - December. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Lee Statue, State Capitol (Richmond, Va.), 1930. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Legislation, Miscellaneous correspondence, 1926. (Box 60, Folder 7-8)
  - Legislation for 1928 Session, 1928. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Legislation, Commission to Promote Uniformity of, 1926-1929. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Legislative Reference Bureau, 1926-1929. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Letters of Commendation, 1927-1928 April. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Letters of Commendation, 1928 May - December. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Letters of Commendation, 1929 January - May. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Letters of Commendation, 1929 June - August. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Letters of Commendation, 1929 September - 1930 January. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Letters to the President, 1926-1930. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Local surveys, 1929. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Lists, 1927-1929. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Lynchings, 1927-1929. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - M, 1926 January - April. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - M, 1926 May - July. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - M, 1926 August - December. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - M, 1927 January - August. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - M, 1927 September - December. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - M, 1928 January - June. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - M, 1928 July - December. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - M, 1929 January - June. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - M, 1929 June - 1930 January. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Madison, James, Monument, undated. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Madison County (Va.), Reception of the President, 1929. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Mailing room, 1927-1928. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Maine, Governor, 1929. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Manassas Battlefield Confederate Park (Va.), 1927. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Manufacturers' Record, 1926-1929. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Queen Marie (Queen of Roumania), 1926. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Markets, Division of, 1927-1929. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Marvel, Josich, 1929. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Maryland, 1926-1929. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Massachusetts, Governor, 1929. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Maury Memorial, 1929. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Meade, Granville P., Estate, 1927. (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Medical College of Virginia, 1925-1928. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Medical College of Virginia, 1929-1930. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Membership of Organizations, 1926-1928. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Membership of Organizations, 1928-1929. (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Messages, 1927. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Miller Manual Labor School, 1927-1930. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Military Board and Rifle Range, 1926-1927. (Box 64, Folder 3-4)
  - Military Board and Rifle Range, 1927-1930. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Mine Inspectors Institute, 1929. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Mineral Resources of Virginia, 1926-1929. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1925-1926. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1926. (Box 64, Folder 9-10)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1929. (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Mumford, Mrs. B.B., 1926. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Motion Picture censorship, 1926-1929. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Motor Vehicles, Automobile insurance licensing, 1926-1929. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Motor Vehicles, Automobile tags, 1927-1929. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, Applicastions for positions within, 1925-1929. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, Booklets 1925-1928. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1925-1926. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1926-1927. (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1927 January - June. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1927 July - December. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1928 January - April. (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1928 May - August. (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1928 September - December. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1929 January - June. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Motor Vehicle Commissioner, 1929 July - 1930 January. (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Mount Vernon, Board of Visitors, 1926-1927. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Mount Vernon, Board of Visitors, 1928. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Multigraphed letters, 1928-1930. (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - N, 1926. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - N, 1927-1929. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Narcotics Conference, 1926-1929. (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - National Conference of State Legislatures, 1926-1927. (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - National Conference of State Parks, 1926-1928. (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - National Conference of Commissioners of Uniform State Law, 1929. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - National Crime Commission, 1926-1927. (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - National Drainage Congress, 1928. (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - National Fire Waste Council, 1929. (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - National Geographic Magazine, 1929. (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - National Guard, 1925. (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - National Park Commission, 1926-1929. (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - National Real Estate Board, 1929. (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - National Recreation Congress, 1926-1929. (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - National Tax Association Congress, 1926. (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - National Tax Association Congress, 1927. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - National Tax Association Congress, 1928-1929. (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Natural Bridge, 1927-1929. (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Naval Academy, 1926-1929. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Near East Relief, 1926-1929. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - New Mexico, 1929. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Newspapers, 1928 November - 1929 May. (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Newspapers, 1929 June - December. (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Newspapers, Associated Press, 1927-1929. (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Newspapers, Editors correspondence, 1929-1930. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers, Subscriptions, 1926-1928. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Newspapers, US Daily, 1929. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Newspapers, Old Bay Colony Magazine, 1927. (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - New York,. (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - New York Bureau of Municipal Research, 1927-1929. (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - New York Fruit Growers trip, 1929. (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Notaries Public, 1926-1929. (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - O, 1926-1929. (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Office hours, 1926. (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Oil pollution, 1926. (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Owens, Dr. Thomas M., 1928. (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Oxford and Cambridge students, 1927-1928. (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Oyster Advisory Commission, 1929. (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Oyster situation, 1926-1927. (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - P, 1926 January - June. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - P, 1926 July - December. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - P, 1927 January - June. (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - P, 1927 July - December. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - P, 1928. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - P, 1929. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Penitentiary, 1925-1926. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Penitentiary, 1927. (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Penitentiary, 1928. (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Penitentiary, 1929 January - June. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Penitentiary, 1929 July - 1930 January. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Penitentiary, Electrocutions, 1926-1929. (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Penitentiary, Governor's Advisory Board on Mental Health, 1926-1928. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Penitentiary, State Convict Road Force, 1926. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Penitentiary, State Convict Road Force, 1927. (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Penitentiary, State Convict Road Force, 1928 January - June. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Penitentiary, State Convict Road Force, 1928 July - December. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Penitentiary, State Convict Road Force, 1929. (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Penitentiary, State Farm, 1925-1929. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Penitentiary, State Lime Grinding Board, 1926-1929. (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Penitentiary, Miscellaneous, 1926. (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - ,. (Box 72)
  - Permanent International Trade Exhibition, 1928-1929. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania, 1929. (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 1926-1929. (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Positions, Misc., 1915-1926. (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Prison Industries Conference, 1926. (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Prisoners, 1927-1929. (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Prisoners, Commission to Study Care and Employment of, 1929-1930. (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Prisoners, Italian, 1927. (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Prisoners and Prison Labor Conference, 1924-1929. (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Proclamations, 1926-1928. (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Proclamations, 1929. (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Program of Progress (Virginia), 1927 December - 1928 Januayr. (Box 73, Folder 1-2)
  - Program of Progress (Virginia), 1928 June - 1930 January. (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Prohibition Dept., 1926-1928. (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Prohibition Dept., 1929. (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Prohibition Dept., Publications, 1924-1928. (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Public Instruction, Superintendent of, 1926-1927. (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Public Instruction, Superintendent of, 1928. (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Public Instruction, Superintendent of, 1929. (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Public printing, 1926-1928. (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Publicity Bureau, 1925-1929. (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Purchasing Agent, Flour, 1926-1929. (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Purchasing and Printing, 1926. (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Purchasing and Printing, 1926-1927. (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Purchasing and Printing, 1928-1929. (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Forfeited cars, 1928 July - October. (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Forfeited cars, 1928 November - December. (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Forfeited cars, 1929 January - February. (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Forfeited cars, 1929 March - April. (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Forfeited cars, 1929 May - August. (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Purchasing and Printing, Forfeited cars, 1929 September - December. (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Q, 1926. (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - R, 1926. (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - R, 1927 January - June. (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - R, 1927 July - December. (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - R, 1928. (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - R, 1929. (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Racetrack Commission, 1928. (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Railroads, 1927-1929. (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Radio, 1927-1930. (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Receiption to British delegation, 1927. (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Reclamations, 1926-1927. (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Recreation, Outdoor Association, 1926. (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Red Cross, 1928-1929. (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Reorganization, 1926. (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Reorganization, 1927 January - February. (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Reorganization, 1927 March. (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Reorganization, 1927 March. (Box 77, Folder 1-3)
  - Reorganization, 1927 April - December. (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Reorganization, 1927 December - 1928 January. (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Reorganization, 1928 March - June. (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Reorganization, 1928 June. (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Reorganization, 1928 June. (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Reorganization, Citizens Committee, 1926-1927. (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Reorganization, Constitutional Amendments, Drafts, 1928. (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Reorganization, Form letters, 1927-1928. (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Reorganization, Newspaper Editors Conference, 1927. (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Reorganization, Publications, 1923-1928. (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Reorganization, Special letters, 1927 March. (Box 78, Folder 7-8)
  - Reorganization, State surveys, Griffenhagen and Associates, Ltd., 1926. (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Reorganization, State surveys, Letters from other state Governors, 1926-1928. (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Reorganization, State surveys, Miscellaneous, 1926. (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Residents, New, Albemarle - Arlington Counties, 1929. (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Residents, New, Carroll - Goochland Counties, 1929. (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Residents, New, Henry - Middlesex Counties, 1929. (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Residents, New, New Kent - Westmoreland Counties, 1929. (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Residents, New, Bristol - Winchester Cities, 1929. (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Residents, New, Miscellaneous, 1929. (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Resolutions, 1927. (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Restoration, Old Hall of House of Delegates, 1927-1929. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Rewards, 1926 - 1927. (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Rewards, 1927 - 1929. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Richmond, Fredericksburg & Potomac Railroad, 1913 - 1929. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Rip Raps Statue Committee, 1928. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Rivers and Harbors Congress, 1925 - 1927. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - S, 1926 January - May. (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - S, 1926 June - July. (Box 80, Folder 8)